<movies>
<movie>
	<id>5189894</id>
	<title>68 Kill</title>
	<year>2017</year>
	<director>Trent Haaga</director>
	<description>A punk-rock after hours about femininity, masculinity and the theft of $68,000.</description>
	<poster>68_kill.jpg</poster>
</movie>
<movie>
	<id>5212918</id>
	<title>A Bad Idea Gone Wrong</title>
	<year>2017</year>
	<director>Jason Headley</director>
	<description>Two would-be thieves forge a surprising relationship with with an unexpected housesitter when they accidentally trap themselves in a house they just broke into.</description>
	<poster>a_bad_idea_gone_wrong.jpg</poster>
</movie>
<movie>
	<id>6218440</id>
	<title>A Critically Endangered Species</title>
	<year>2017</year>
	<director>Zachary Cotler, Magdalena Zyzak</director>
	<description>This is the story of Maya Dardel, a famous poet and novelist who decides to commit suicide and announces the fact on national radio.</description>
	<poster>a_critically_endangered_species.jpg</poster>
</movie>
<movie>
	<id>4411466</id>
	<title>California Dreams</title>
	<year>2017</year>
	<director>Mike Ott</director>
	<description>A journey into the hallucination of cinema.</description>
	<poster>california_dreams.jpg</poster>
</movie>
<movie>
	<id>4680182</id>
	<title>Colossal</title>
	<year>2016</year>
	<director>Nacho Vigalondo</director>
	<description>Gloria is an out-of-work party girl forced to leave her life in New York City, and move back home. When reports surface that a giant creature is destroying Seoul, she gradually comes to the realization that she is somehow connected to this phenomenon.</description>
	<poster>colossal.jpg</poster>
</movie>
<movie>
	<id>3212026</id>
	<title>Dara Ju</title>
	<year>2017</year>
	<director>Anthony Onah</director>
	<description>A young Nigerian-American financier struggles with love, family, and a prescription drug dependency as his ambitions steer him down a criminal path.</description>
	<poster>daraju.jpg</poster>
</movie>
<movie>
	<id>6180842</id>
	<title>Drib</title>
	<year>2017</year>
	<director>Kristoffer Borgli</director>
	<description>The inside story of an energy drink marketing ploy gone wrong.</description>
	<poster>drib.jpg</poster>
</movie>
<movie>
	<id>3416536</id>
	<title>Hot Summer Nights</title>
	<year>2017</year>
	<director>Elijah Bynum</director>
	<description>A boy comes of age during a summer he spends in Cape Cod.</description>
	<poster>hot_summer_nights.jpg</poster>
</movie>
<movie>
	<id>3896738</id>
	<title>Hounds of Love</title>
	<year>2016</year>
	<director>Ben Young</director>
	<description>A cold-blooded predatory couple while cruising the streets in search of their next victim, will stumble upon a 17-year-old high school girl, who will be sedated, abducted and chained in the strangers' guest room.</description>
	<poster>hounds_of_love.jpg</poster>
</movie>
<movie>
	<id>4135326</id>
	<title>Lane 1974</title>
	<year>2017</year>
	<director>S.J. Chiro</director>
	<description>Based on a true story, Lane is a 13-year-old girl coming of age on a Northern California commune in the 1970s. While Lane enjoys the freedom of living off-the-grid with her mother and younger siblings, she craves a stable ""normal"" life - a life she's only seen in pictures from a stolen Sears catalog. Lane must navigate her troubled mother, Hallelujah, while trying to care for her younger brother and sister. After a series of dangerous and isolating events, Lane decides to forge her own path in hopes of finding a better life after it becomes clear her family has fallen apart.</description>
	<poster>lane1974.jpg</poster>
</movie>
<movie>
	<id>5091530</id>
	<title>M.F.A.</title>
	<year>2017</year>
	<director>Natalia Leite</director>
	<description>An art student taps into a rich source of creative inspiration after the accidental slaughter of her rapist. An unlikely vigilante emerges, set out to avenge college girls whose attackers walked free- all the while fueling a vivid thesis exhibition.</description>
	<poster>mfa.jpg</poster>
</movie>
<movie>
	<id>5707304</id>
	<title>Madre</title>
	<year>2016</year>
	<director>Aaron Burns</director>
	<description>Diana Prieto is pregnant and taking care of her autistic son Martin has become overwhelming. She has no one to help her while her husband Tomas spends months working in Asia. Diana's at her breaking point with Martin when Luz, a gifted caregiver from the Philippines, steps in to help. Martin quickly begins improving under Luz's supervision, but Diana's worried that he's only being taught to speak Filipino. Diana begins to suspect that Luz is using the language barrier and voodoo to turn Martin against Diana and into something far more sinister...</description>
	<poster>madre.jpg</poster>
</movie>
<movie>
	<id>6212496</id>
	<title>Mr. Roosevelt</title>
	<year>2017</year>
	<director>Noël Wells</director>
	<description>After a loved one falls ill, struggling comedian Emily Martin returns to her college town of Austin, Texas and must come to terms with her past while staying with her ex-boyfriend and his new girlfriend.</description>
	<poster>mr_roosevelt.jpg</poster>
</movie>
<movie>
	<id>6333064</id>
	<title>Nobody Speak: Trials of the Free Press</title>
	<year>2017</year>
	<director>Brian Knappenberger</director>
	<description>The trial between Hulk Hogan and Gawker Media pitted privacy rights against freedom of the press, and raised important questions about how big money can silence media. This film is an examination of the perils and duties of the free press in an age of inequality.</description>
	<poster>nobody_speak.jpg</poster>
</movie>
<movie>
	<id>5154288</id>
	<title>Prevenge</title>
	<year>2016</year>
	<director>Alice Lowe</director>
	<description>Widow Ruth is seven months pregnant when, believing herself to be guided by her unborn baby, she embarks on a homicidal rampage, dispatching anyone who stands in her way.</description>
	<poster>prevenge.jpg</poster>
</movie>
<movie>
	<id>5806646</id>
	<title>The Archer</title>
	<year>2017</year>
	<director>Valerie Weiss</director>
	<description>Lauren Pierce has just become the high-school Tri-State Archery Champion. After the competition, Lauren and her teammate Emily return to their hotel room for a night of irresponsible celebratory drinking that grows into more. When interrupted by Emily's abusive boyfriend, Lauren snaps and brutally beats Daniel. Lauren is then sentenced to a girls' reform camp Paradise Ridge, nestled in the mountains of California. But this ""reform camp"" turns out to be a corrupt and twisted prison that breaks young girls and keeps parents in the dark .With the help of Rebecca, a strong and provocative young woman whom Lauren befriends, the two escape the unsafe facility and fight for their lives out in the Utah wilderness; a journey of growth, acceptance and resilience of what they believe is right.</description>
	<poster>the_archer.jpg</poster>
</movie>
<movie>
	<id>5462602</id>
	<title>The Big Sick</title>
	<year>2017</year>
	<director>Michael Showalter</director>
	<description>A couple deals with their cultural differences as their relationship grows.</description>
	<poster>big_sick.jpg</poster>
</movie>
<movie>
	<id>4842646</id>
	<title>The Most Hated Woman in America</title>
	<year>2017</year>
	<director>Tommy O'Haver</director>
	<description>The life of Madelyn Murray O'Hair, the outspoken activist and founder of American Atheists.</description>
	<poster>the_most_hated_woman_in_america.jpg</poster>
</movie>
<movie>
	<id>2088950</id>
	<title>This Is Your Death</title>
	<year>2017</year>
	<director>Giancarlo Esposito</director>
	<description>An unsettling look at reality T.V. where a disturbing hit game show has its contestants ending their lives for the public's enjoyment.</description>
	<poster>this_is_your_death.jpg</poster>
</movie>
<movie>
	<id>3268850</id>
	<title>Unrest</title>
	<year>2017</year>
	<director>Jennifer Brea</director>
	<description>When Harvard Ph.D. student Jennifer Brea is struck down by a fever that leaves her bedridden, she sets out on a virtual journey to document her story as she fights a disease that medicine forgot.</description>
	<poster>unrest.jpg</poster>
</movie>
</movies>